{
  "extraDescription": "Recall cubes of 0-10",
  "randomQuestionCount": 2,
  "questions": [
    {
      "question": "3&sup3;",
      "answer": "27"
    },
    {
      "question": "7&sup3;",
      "answer": "343"
    },
    {
      "question": "1&sup3;",
      "answer": "1"
    },
    {
      "question": "0&sup3;",
      "answer": "0"
    },
    {
      "question": "5&sup3;",
      "answer": "125"
    },
    {
      "question": "10&sup3;",
      "answer": "1000"
    },
    {
      "question": "9&sup3;",
      "answer": "729"
    },
    {
      "question": "2&sup3;",
      "answer": "8"
    },
    {
      "question": "8&sup3;",
      "answer": "512"
    },
    {
      "question": "4&sup3;",
      "answer": "64"
    },
    {
      "question": "6&sup3;",
      "answer": "216"
    }
  ]
}
